https://www.purefjcruiser.com/index.php?main_page=privacy

Light Mounts & Kits
Lights (Off-Road)
Rugged Ridge
S.M.D.
Optimus Series
Optimus Series (Round)
About Us
Welcome to PURE FJ CRUISER!
At PURE FJ CRUISER, you will find the largest selection of FJ Cruiser parts and accessories on the web. We are dedicated to providing you with the best customer service around.
Information
Customer Service
About Us
Log In
Create Account
Shipping & Returns
Privacy Notice
Conditions of Use
Please Select
Accessories Unlimite..
Addictive Desert Des..
AEM
Aeroflow
AFE Power
Air Lift
AIRAID
AirBedz
All Sales (AMI)
All-Pro Off-Road
Amsteel
Anzo
ARB
Aries
Aspire Auto Accessor..
Au-ve-co
Auto Dolly By Merric..
Autometer
AVS
B&I
B-Dawg
Badge Store USA
Baja Designs
Baja Rack
Banks Power
Cascadia4x4
Clazzio / Eleven Int..
Cobra Electronics
Coleman
Comeup
Corsa
Covercraft
CSF, Inc
Currie Enterprises
Curt Mfg
Fox Shox
Front Runner Outfitt..
Fuel
G2 Axle and Gear
Galaxy Radios
Garvin Industries
Go Power
Go Rhino
Gorilla
Green Filter
Hypertech
Icon Vehicle Dynamic..
Injen
Interco
IPCW
Ironman
JACO
JBA
Jet Chips
JT's Differentials
RCI Metalworks
RCV Performance Prod..
ReadyLift
Real Wheels
Remmen Brakes
Revolution Gear & Ax..
Revtek
Rhino-Rack
Ricochet Off-Road Ar..
Rigid Industries
RK Sport
Road Armor
ROAM Adventure Co.
Rokmen Off Road
Rola
Rotopax
Rough Country
Rugged Ridge
Scepter
Scosche
Shrockworks
Skidmark 4x4
SMD Lights
Smittybilt
Southern Style Off-R..
Specialty Products C..
Spidertrax
sPOD
Sprint Booster
Spyder Auto
Stant
Super Bright
Superlift
Sway-A-Way
Toyota
Toyota Racing Develo..
Toytec
Trail Gear
TrailReady
Trasharoo
Tuffy Products
Twisted Pro All-Terr..
Underdog Racing Deve..
Uniden
US Speedo
Versahaul
Vi-Store
VIAIR
Viking Off-Road
Vision X
Volant
Categories
Pure FJ Branded PartsAir Intakes/FiltersBadges & EmblemsBlack Out PartsBrake Pads & RotorsBumpersBumpers In StockCamping GearCB RadiosDash CamerasDrivetrainElectronicsExhaust SystemsExterior AccessoriesFirst AidFuel Cans/Related PartsGenuine Toyota PartsGrille GuardsGrille InsertsHitch AccessoriesHoods & AccessoriesInterior AccessoriesLED LightingLight Mounts & KitsLights (Off-Road)Lights - AssembliesMaintenanceNight Run FunOff-Road AccessoriesPerformance PartsPet Safety/Seat BeltsRecovery GearRoof Rack AccessoriesRoof RacksSecurity LockboxesSkid PlatesSliders / Nerf Bars / StepsSound Deadening/InsulationStereo / AudioSuspension / Lift KitsTire CoversTiresWheelsWinchesUniversal AccessoriesAFE PowerARBBaja RackCali Raised LEDDB CustomzDemello Off-RoadExpedition OneFactor 55Fourtreks MountsFront RunnerIcon Vehicle DynamicsIPCWMetal Tech 4x4Military Surplus GearOrange BoxxRAD Rubber DesignRCI Off-RoadRhino-RackTJM AccessoriesTrail Gear ProductsWarrior ProductsXK GlowFJ Summit PrepScratch & Dent FJ Cruiser PartsGift CertificatesSpecialsNew ProductsAll Products ...
Information
About Us
Shipping & Returns
Privacy Notice
Conditions of Use
Contact Us
Site Map
Gift Certificate FAQ
Privacy Policy
Here at PURE FJ CRUISER, a Pure Auto Parts Inc company,
we understand the importance of maintaining our customers privacy online. We understand that in this time of spam e-mail, and credit card fraud our customers want to know and have the right to know how personal information is handled.
What information is needed from our customers?
When placing an order on our website certain information is needed to processes the order. Your name and billing address associated with the credit card you are using, your credit card information, e-mail address and shipping address.
We may sometimes need more than one address from you.
In most cases we only need one address. But if your product is shipping to a different location than your billing address, we will need both addresses. In order to eliminate credit card fraud we can only process your credit card if your billing information matches the credit card you provide. While we will ship to any location within the continental US, your shipping information does not need to match the billing information.
What happens to your information after we collect it?
The information you provided us is used only to complete your order. Your credit card is processed, the billing address you provided is then matched to protect against fraud. Only your shipping address and product information goes to our shipping department and possibly an off location warehouse. Please be assured that all billing and credit card information is never shared with any third party. It is stored encrypted on our website for your review and updating at any time by logging into your account.
Is my credit card information safe?
Yes. PURE FJ CRUISER uses SSL (Secure Socket Layer) technology to encrypt your information. When you click on the "create account" or "checkout" button you will notice the browser change from http:// to https://. This indicates a secure website. You may also see a lock in the bottom right of your browser. Depending on your browser you may also have a box appear stating you are about to view information over a secure connection. Once your credit card information is entered and submitted with your order, the credit card information is destroyed. This is why we ask for your credit card information again if you place several orders with us, we don't store it.
When is my credit card charged?
PURE FJ CRUISER charges your credit card when you submit your order online. If there is a delay in shipping your order, you will be notified by phone or email within 2 business days.
Will my e-mail address be given out to anyone else?
PURE FJ CRUISER does not sell, or give out any personal information including your e-mail address to any third-parties. The information you provide to us, stays with us. PURE FJ CRUISER may compose and send out newsletters on occasion and therefore we will use your e-mail address to keep you informed on new products and specials. If you do not wish to receive our newsletter there is a location registration that allows you to choose your preference for that.
When using PURE FJ CRUISER, you are subject to the terms above. We will keep your information confidential and secure. Please e-mail us with any questions or comments about this policy. Send correspondence to orders@purefjcruiser.com.
Back
Search
Advanced Search
Important Links
FJ Cruiser Technical Docs
Gallery
Pure FJ FAQ
Manufacturer Discounts
10% off on all products made by Bushwacker10% off on all products made by N-Fab10% off on all products made by AVS
Shop by Price
$0 - $50
$50 - $100
$100 - $200
$200 - $300
$300 and above
Have you seen ...
PayPal Credit
Bestsellers
Au-ve-co FJ Cruiser Cowl Clip Set$14.15
REVEAL MOLDING RETAINER$3.45
RAD Rubber FJ Engine Splash Guards$49.95
Shop
Home
Featured
Share and Connect
Copyright © 2020 PURE FJ CRUISER.
* Continental USA Only. WARNING: This product may contain chemicals knownto the State of California to cause cancer, birth defectsand other reproductive harm.
Site Map
Privacy Notice
Conditions of Use
Your IP Address is:
72.182.10.230
